ISABAJO IDRIS ADETAYO

37 Olakunle Shoga Street, Haruna, Ikorodu Tel: 07053166294, 08165717648 Email: idrisisabajo@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Self-motivated Web Developer with comprehensive experience managing multiple clients. Passionate and hardworking to deliver on deadlines. Strong HTML and CSS programmer. To be actively involved in making sure that my company continually meets and exceeds its goals and targets. To establish myself in a challenging working environment that offers opportunities for career growth.

OTHER PERSONAL DATA

Date of birth

21st, July 1989

Sex

Male

Marital status

Married

State of origin

Lagos

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

Ajayi Crowther University, Oyo State.

Bsc. Computer Science - Second Class Upper Division.

2020-2022

The Federal Polytechnic Ilaro, Ogun State

Higher National Diploma (HND) - Distinction in Computer Engineering

2010-2012

Lagos State Polytechnic, Ikorodu, Lagos.

National Diploma (ND) in Computer Technology Engineering

2007-2009

Tesmoh Comprehensive College, Agiliti Phase II, Lagos

West Africa Senior Secondary School Certificate

2002-2005

The Apostolic Church Grammar School, Ketu, Lagos

1999-2002

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Care Officer and Tellering

Access Bank PLC, 533 Ikorodu Road,

Jun 2018 - Jan 2022

Ketu, Lagos

ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:

Treating customers' requests in line with the rules and regulation of the bank.

- Using both banking and business applications to resolve customers complaints and requests.
- Ensuring proper facilitation of information between all business functions within the boundaries of the organization
- Managing the process of planning, implementing and maintaining equipment and facilities.

Customer Care Officer

Access Bank PLC, Ojodu Branch, Ojota, Lagos

Dec 2014 - Jun 2018

ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:

- Treating customers' requests in line with the rules and regulation of the bank.
- Using banking applications like CRM Dynamics, Tuga, Process maker and other business
 applications to process customers' requests and to increase productivity.
- Ensuring the effective flow of services and information from their origin.
- Ensuring customers have a good experience while resolving their complaints
- Ensuring proper facilitation of information between all business functions within the boundaries of the organization.
- Delivering quality service with the right attitude

Mathematics and Computer Science Teacher National Youth Service Corps (NYSC)

Oct 2012- Nov 2013

Community High School, Elekokan, Iwajowa LGA, Oyo State, Nigeria

- Teaching introduction to computer studies
- Assisting the sports master.
- Supervision of examinations

HARDWARE ENGINEER (INDUSTRIAL TRAINEE)

Datagem Systems Limited, 47, Akeju Street, Lagos, Nigeria

Jan - Nov. 2010

ROLES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:

- · Keeping of records and entering of data making use of excel sheet
- Ensuring all the systems are in good working condition.
- · Maintaining inventory of all network devices
- Installations and troubleshooting faulty computer systems
- Managing and monitoring LAN/WAN network service.

PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATION

| Javascript Full Stack Web Development, Tech Studio Academy | Jun 2022 |
|--|----------|
| Certificate of Completion on Administrative Staff Training Program | |
| Access Bank | Jul 2016 |
| Personal Branding and Emotional Intelligence | |
| (Access Bank Plc) | Jul 2016 |
| A+ training (Certification), New Horizons, Ikeja, Lagos. | In view |
| CCNA training, New Horizons, Ikeja, Lagos. | In view |

SKILLS AND ATTRIBUTES

- Hardworking and self-motivated
- Leadership and analytical skills
- Great interpersonal skill and excellent communication skills
- A broad knowledge of varieties of application software including Microsoft office (word, excel, power point etc)
- Team player and highly resourceful.
- Good application of HTML coding, JavaScript, CSS.

HOBBIES

Reading, travelling and swimming

REFEREES

Available on request